<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vai Ali Pra Mim</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mapa">Map</string>
    <string name="cadastro">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="data_cad">Date of birth</string>
    <string name="cpf_cad">CPF</string>
    <string name="email_cad">Email</string>
    <string name="msg_confirmacaoEmail">A verification code has been sent to:</string>
    <string name="msg_insrecaoEmail">Enter the code received below</string>
    <string name="senha_cad" translatable="false">Password</string>
    <string name="confSenha_cad">Confirm password</string>
    <string name="Telefone_cad">Telephone</string>
    <string name="check_cad">Do you want to be a delivery man?</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="edit_perf">Edit profile</string>
    <string name="conf">Settings</string>
    <string name="term">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="aval">Rate us</string>
    <string name="perfil">Profile</string>
    <string name="nav_fechar">Close</string>
    <string name="nav_abrir">Open</string>
    <string name="nome_user">User Name</string>
    <string name="ent_pen">Pending deliveries</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="saldo_user">R$ 17,00</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="texto_tc">"1. Acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of Use The use of the comment tool (hereinafter referred to as the Tool) offered by Editora Abril on its Vip website is subject to acceptance and compliance with the Terms and Conditions of Use described below. To make use of the Tool and post comments it is necessary to: (i) carefully read the terms described below; (ii) expressly agree with them; and (iii) provide a valid email address when posting any content on the Site. By using the Tool offered by Editora Abril S / A (hereinafter referred to as Abril), you (hereinafter referred to as User) agree that you have read, understood and accepted the terms, rules and conditions set forth herein. The Terms and Conditions of Use regulate the use of the Site and the Tool, which belong to Editora Abril S / A, located at Avenida das Nações Unidas, No. 7221, São Paulo SP, duly registered with CNPJ / MF under No. 02.183.757 / 0004 36. The Tool is available to those with civilian capacity to use it. If the User does not have the capacity to contract or use the Tool, when User is mentioned in this Term then it will also be understood that the declarations have been made by his legal guardian. Abril reserves the right to modify the presentation, configuration and availability of the Tool and or the Site at any time. The same applies to these Terms and Conditions of Use, established as a fundamental condition for using the service. 2. Comments Tool Abril offers the User a tool that allows the publication of texts on the Site, in the form of a User comment, which will be hosted on Abril's servers. 3. Free of charge The Tool is offered to the User free of charge. The values ​​referring to the use of the services necessary to access the Internet, among others, are the exclusive responsibility of the User. 4. Use of the Tool The User acknowledges that he is responsible for any false information that may be provided for the use of the tool, as well as for any comment or content inserted by him on the Site. The User exempts Abril from any responsibility regarding the veracity of the personal data provided by him when using the Tool, as well as for any violation of the rights of third parties, which occurred through the tool on the Site resulting from his declarations. The user also recognizes that these Terms and Conditions of Use of the Tool offered by Abril must be observed and faithfully complied with, under penalty of canceling the blocking of the use of the Tool and other applicable measures, in case the aforementioned Terms are violated or breached. 5. Registration and personal data It is the User's duty to keep updated the personal data provided when using the Tool. The Company may cancel any registration of the User, at any time and without prior notice, as soon as it becomes aware, and at its sole discretion, if the User violates these Terms and Conditions of Use, whether intentionally or unintentionally, or violates federal laws and regulations. , state and / or municipal, or violate legal principles, morals and good customs. Users who have their registrations canceled will no longer be able to use the Tool. 6. User conduct rules The User undertakes not to use the Tool for the publication, creation, storage and / or dissemination of: a) Abusive content, such as defamatory, discriminatory, obscene texts, photos and / or videos , offensive, threatening, abusive, vexatious, harmful, that contains expressions of hatred against people or groups, or that contains child pornography, explicit or violent pornography, content that may be harmful to minors, that contains religious or racial insults or threats, or that encourages moral (including bodily) and property damage, or that may violate any third party right, notably human rights. b) Advertising banners and / or any type of electronic commerce that is considered illegal, thus understood those that are contrary to the law or offend the rights of third parties. c) Any type of material (texts, photos and / or videos) protected by copyrights, copyright or that, for any reason, violate the rights of third parties. d) Defamatory and slanderous information or that are contrary to honor, personal and family intimacy or to the image of people (including legal entities, entities and organizations and the like). e) Material that incites violence and crime, as well as product piracy. f) Content that causes damage to the Abril system, due to its characteristics (such as file extensions and file formats). The User agrees that, when using the Tool, he / she will not: violate any of these Terms and Conditions of Use; practice falsehood, thus understood to be false information (ie: purposeful and voluntary disclosure of information that the User knows to be false or that is notoriously false) and ideological falsehood; post or transmit any abusive or offensive content in the comments; replicate or store abusive content on Abril's servers; do anything or perform any act contrary to the good faith and the habits and customs of the virtual communities and that may offend any right of third parties. Violations of the uses and customs of virtual communities must also be understood as the excessive use of capitalized text, the use of offensive criticism (known as \"flamming\"), the unnecessary and reckless inclusion of previous communications in any publication or transmission, as well as any other act that is at odds with the commonly accepted Internet etiquette. commit fraud; violate or infringe intellectual property rights, fiduciary or contractual rights, privacy or publicity rights of others; propagate, distribute or transmit destructive codes, whether or not they have caused real damage; gather personal or commercial data, including (but not limited to) e-mail addresses and / or names of any Internet resource, whether managed by us or by third parties, for commercial, political, charitable or other purposes, without consent of the owners of such data; reproduce, replicate, copy, alter, modify, create derivative works from, sell or resell any of Abril's services or any part thereof, including websites and web pages, or the information or data contained in Abril's services; carry out political propaganda in the comments; use robots, spiders or any other device, automatic or manual, to monitor or copy any content on Abril's service; transmit content that does not belong to the User or that he has no right to publish or distribute, whether under law or contract; access the Tool without authorization, through hacking, password mining or any other fraudulent means or that represents a violation of the rights of third parties; carry out or encourage illegal activities, including (but not limited to) promoting or facilitating access, use or sale of dangerous substances or devices; fail to comply with any applicable laws, rules, rules, principles and regulations; help any third party to carry out any of the actions prohibited by these Terms and Conditions of Use. Abril has the right to remove User comments (s) if it considers that this content is inappropriate or inappropriate, in violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use, legislation or any third party right. Abril reserves the right to check or moderate the content of the comments posted through its comments tool at any time, if deemed necessary, as indicated in item 11 of these Terms. 7. Intellectual Property Rights Abril respects the intellectual property rights of third parties and requires Users to do the same. When submitting any content or information to the Site, including texts, such as comments through the Tool, discussion forums, communities, polls, tests, doubts section, participation in cultural contest, photographs, illustrations, videos, audio files and others materials, the User declares to authorize, free of charge, non-exclusive, perpetual, global and royalty-free, the use of the material by Abril and its affiliates and partners, by any modality and support, for publication, reproduction, transmission, retransmission, distribution, communication to the public, editing, adaptation and other transformations, translation into any language, inclusion in any other works, representation, execution, use by broadcasting and other means of communication, through the use of any technology, exhibition, inclusion on a data and any other modalities of use existing or that may be invented in the future, on any existing media or to be invented in the future, also authorizing the creation of derivative works and the sub-licensing of the material for use in other Abril communication platforms, with no time limit and territory. Any eventual omission will not imply a limitation on the use of the material by Abril. If the User does not agree to authorize Abril to use its contribution as above, the User must not submit any material to the Site. All patrimonial copyrights on the material submitted by the User remain their property and their name will be mentioned whenever the material is used by Abril, as informed by the User, unless the space or physical support in which it appears does not allow this citation. . Abril is not obliged to use the materials sent by the User and is authorized to edit the comments sent by the User. The User acknowledges and declares that in any contribution submitted to the Site, the corresponding material is of his exclusive creation, not constituting a violation of copyrights, brands, secrets, personality rights, including honor, intimacy, private life and the image of people , property rights and any other rights of third parties and which has powers to authorize the use of the material by Abril as above. As long as the source is cited (including the author's name, when possible and applicable) and within the conditions and limits provided by law, notably the Copyright Law (Law No. 9,610 / 98), the User cannot reproduce, publish , present, rent, offer or display any copy of any content belonging to Abril without the consent of Abril or, in the case of content authored by third parties, without the consent of the author. The User undertakes to comply with all national and international laws regarding Intellectual Property Rights. 8. Reporting abuse and violation The User undertakes to report any abuse or violation of these Terms and Conditions of Use or any third party rights that he observes and / or is a victim of when using the Tool. The User must click Report abuse in the comments. All content that the User publishes using the Tool is information that, by its nature and characteristic, is public, open and non-confidential. By revealing personal data, such as his name and e-mail address in the comments, the User accepts and understands that this information can be collected and used by other people to communicate with him, without any liability being attributed to Abril. Therefore, Abril recommends that the User is, therefore, careful when deciding to share any personal data on the Site. 9. Responsibilities The User is legally responsible for the content of his comments on the Tool. Abril is not responsible for any damages suffered by the User or third parties that, in any way, have origin or dependence related to the Tool. Abril disclaims any liability for losses resulting from any interruption or error on the Abril virtual website, including the inability to access the website and / or the websites related to it. Abril does not own the products offered by Merchants [or Advertisers], does not own them, does not carry out sales offers, nor does it intervene in the delivery of products, the negotiation of which begins on the website. The User acknowledges that there is no involvement or intervention by Abril in the deals entered into with the Merchants on the Vip website. In no case will Abril be liable for any damage or loss suffered by the User as a result of the negotiations carried out through the Vip website, due to the conduct of the Merchants, including, but not limited to, fraud or fraud on line. Abril is under no obligation to control, and effectively does not control, the offer and sale of Products in third-party Virtual Stores, the conditions for the sale of Products established by Merchants, and the fulfillment, by the Merchant, of the obligations arising from the offer and commercialization of the products. Abril is also not responsible for the transaction made between User and Merchant, for the effective fulfillment of the obligations assumed by the Merchants, nor for the existence, quantity, quality, status, lawfulness, integrity or legitimacy of the products offered and / or sold by the Merchants on the Vip site . Abril does not grant guarantees for hidden or apparent defects in products and / or in negotiations between Users and Traders. The User acknowledges and accepts that, when carrying out negotiations with the Merchants, he does so at his own risk, exempting Abril of any responsibility 10. Data privacy Abril is not responsible for any damages that the User may suffer, which may originate disclosure of the User's personal data or that of third parties in materials published in the comments. Abril preserves the privacy of the Users' data, and undertakes to reveal the User's personal data only for one of the following reasons: by law; through an order or subpoena from a body, authority or court empowered and with competent jurisdiction; to guarantee the security of the systems, safeguard rights and prevent Abril's responsibilities. 11. Applicable legislation These Terms and Conditions of Use are governed and interpreted according to the laws of the Federative Republic of Brazil and all disputes, actions and other related matters will be determined in accordance with this legislation.  "</string>
    <string name="nome_cad">Full Name</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="fire">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="valor">Add</string>
    <string name="email_login">Email</string>
    <string name="facaLogin">LOG IN</string>
    <string name="senha_login">Password</string>
    <string name="esqueceu_senha">Forgot your password?</string>
    <string name="tern_cond">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="impot_tern">IMPORTANT</string>
    <string name="leia_tern">Read and accept the Terms and Conditions to proceed</string>
    <string name="aceitacao_tern">I accept the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="hist_ent">Delivery history</string>
    <string name="extrato">Extract</string>
    <string name="ped_sol">Requested orders</string>
    <string name="entPen_timeL">Pending deliveries</string>
    <string name="postar">Post</string>
    <string name="nome_estab">Name of the establishment:</string>
    <string name="exemp_nomeEstab">Example: Padaria Santana</string>
    <string name="quant_itens">Maximum number of items:</string>
    <string name="exemp_quantIntens">Example: 10</string>
    <string name="peso_itens">Maximum weight of items:</string>
    <string name="exemp_peso">Example: 2.5</string>
    <string name="taxa_entr">Delivery fee:</string>
    <string name="exemp_taxa">Example: 3.15</string>
    <string name="exemp_temp">Exemplo: 1h</string>
    <string name="temp_comp">Estimated time to purchase:</string>
    <string name="data_horaReal">Date and time the service will be performed:</string>
    <string name="data_ped">DATE REQUESTED</string>
    <string name="preco_priItem">PRICE FIRST ITEM</string>
    <string name="preco_segItem">SECOND PRICE ITEM</string>
    <string name="aceitar">Accept</string>
    <string name="rejeitar">Reject</string>
    <string name="voltar">Come back</string>
    <string name="sair">Go out</string>
    <string name="valor_total">total purchase amount: R$ 2330</string>
    <string name="pedidos_solicitados">Requested Orders</string>
</resources>